hello everyone
today we woke up confined on a floating island
but since there's a tree with us
we can use that to expand our landscape
not satisfied with the wood parquet
we started moving around the dirt to extract some stones
but those rocks were too rough
so we sifted out the various sizes
and it was then that we found some minerals
we used those to build some spinning machines
leading to a steam revolution
we further improved our technology with electricity
to the point of making an electric blast furnace
and to further speed up our progression
we automated everything
from wood collection to a to auto crafting
and now that we automated automation
we can quickly dash through HV
and build a clean room for the EV machinery
to power all of that
we built a couple of steam turbines
then we processed our mineral byproducts
enough to collect some tungsten and platinum
allowing us to build the good multi blocks
and on top of that
we also have some perfectly overclocking multi blocks
which we are now powering with some nuclear reactors
building all of those reactors reminded us that
it was time to assemble a fusion reactor
however, that didn't look good enough
so we built a research station to research a better version
but not even those fusion reactors satisfied us
so after building a couple more
we figured out we should invest in more computation power to unlock a better reactor
and talking about plasma hot machines
we should also have a heat chamber
which goes side by side with a mega blast furnace
but of course nothing shall be taller than our Fusion Tower
and after building such a long thing
we can chill with some BBC
once everything is cool enough
we then start vibrating like a strobe blazer
finally, once we realize how awful those jokes were
we build a dimensional finder to find a place to hide
such place wasn't behind our new toys
but a new dimension which can only be reached by playing with those long enough
however  staring at our latest toy scared us
following our instinct
we built an exponential amount of fusion reactors
to obtain the mental fortitude required to try it out
with all of that power
we turned on its lights
and just when we thought we were done with the DTPF toy
a dark bubble randomly appeared
upon further inspection
it turned out to be some sort of portal
which brought us into a weird temple
this place looked so old
that who built it probably became oil
and after extracting said oil
we started digging a path into the secret rooms hidden in this place
here we found some ancient technological artifacts
which however seemed to be broken
but more interestingly
there was a suspicious device that looked like an elevator that was still working
that device brought us in a room on a familiar corridor
but most interestingly to a research station
by using it
we figured out how to repair the ancient artifacts
all we needed was some good lubricant
made by (Dutan Commons oil ?)
and with the help of some DNA disks
we managed to extract the information required to craft the ancient runic circuits
now we can go back on our straight path
and build some new machines that will greatly improve our ability to gather and process materials
to power all of that
we tried building new turbines
but the Pharaoh curse caused sand to clog those
so we built a supreme turbine that can withstand the sand curse
that turbine was also really plasma hungry
so we had to build an auxiliary fusion reactor to keep up with it
and after building enough of those
we started playing with some bacteria we found on Tutankhamun body
after enough mutations
we managed to secure a good source of hydrocarbons
which we use to build a Runic manifold manipulator
this machine will use the product of our newly grown fusion reactors
to fold the structure parts required for our new Runic Stargate assembler
with it  we can restore the ancient Stargate
which will bring us in a dier place
we wandered around for some time
finding all sorts of fluids
but what mostly attracted our curiosity was a husk of the flame
after studying it
with the help of some heavily processed nether rack
we managed to build a hell forge
and while that isn't as good as a god forge
it still produced some quite good plasma
which we cooled down in our new Quantum Chiller
but our metalworking still wasn't fast enough
luckily we received a helping hand from the sky
that allowed us to build a mega alloy blast smelter
but now we had too much stuff to cool down
and just quantum cooling wasn't good enough
hoping to promote our vacuum freezer to void freezer
we built yet another star gate towards the end dimension
where we started collecting gas as usual
we then proceeded into a quick expedition to locate a dragon head
which we used to research our new draconic infusion array
with this we can now upgrade our technology
such as the 48 Blocks Range wireless power transmitter
which not only allows us to use wireless energy
but also 64 amps hatches
we also gained access to the next tier of fusion reactors
but most importantly
we can now make a room that is cleaner than a sterile room
this room is indeed filled with the breath of an ancient dragon
allowing for the crafting of the highest level of draconian technology
which will culminate with the second tier of auxiliary boosted fusion reactor
capable of producing maxwellium
and after quickly crafting all the parts required for the structure of that new machine
we finally completed it and obtained a new friend
since he's going to stick with us for a while
we pick him up so that we can show his new home
this is the place where bad boys get corrected
this is where we craft hot fluids
this is where we craft hotter fluids
this is where we craft hot solids
next to it, we cool down the hot materials
those are our assembly lines
this is our main battery
the supreme turbines that charge our batteries
random machines doing passive processes
random machines crafting whatever we need
your Mama
expensive
ruins of the old fusion reactors
your siblings
and that's your new playground
please be careful and don't twist the fabric of space time
大家好
今天我们在一个漂浮的岛上醒来
但既然我们有一棵树
我们可以用它来扩展我们的景观
对木地板不满意
我们开始在泥土周围移动以提取一些石头
但那些石头太粗糙了
所以我们筛选出各种尺寸
就在那时我们发现了一些矿物质
我们用它们来制造纺纱机
导致蒸汽革命
我们用电力进一步改进了我们的技术
达到制造电炉的程度
为了进一步加快我们的进程
我们自动化了一切
从木材收集到汽车工艺
现在我们实现了自动化
我们可以快速冲过高压
为电动汽车机器建一个无尘室
为这一切提供动力
我们造了几个汽轮机
然后我们加工我们的矿物副产品
足够收集一些钨和铂
允许我们建造好的多街区
最重要的是
我们还有一些完美的超频多块
我们现在正在用一些核反应堆供电
建造所有这些反应堆提醒我们
是时候组装一个核聚变反应堆了
然而，这看起来还不够好
所以我们建了一个研究站来研究更好的版本
但即使是那些核聚变反应堆也不能让我们满意
所以在再建几个之后
我们发现我们应该投资更多的计算能力来解锁一个更好的反应堆。
谈论等离子热机器
我们还应该有个热室
它与一个巨型高炉并排
当然没有比我们的融合塔更高的了
在建造了这么长的东西之后
我们可以听一些英国广播公司的节目
一旦一切都足够酷
然后我们开始像频闪西装外套一样振动
最后，一旦我们意识到那些笑话有多糟糕
我们建造一个维度发现者来寻找藏身之处
这样的地方不在我们的新玩具后面
而是一个新的维度，只有和那些人玩足够长的时间才能达到
然而盯着我们最新的玩具吓坏了我们
跟随我们的直觉
我们建造了指数数量的核聚变反应堆
以获得尝试所需的精神毅力
有了所有的力量
我们打开了它的灯
就在我们以为我们已经完成了DTPF玩具的时候
一个黑暗的气泡随机出现
经进一步检查
原来是某种传送门
这把我们带到了一个奇怪的寺庙
这地方看起来好旧
建造它的人可能变成了石油
提取上述油后
我们开始挖一条路进入这个地方隐藏的密室
在这里我们发现了一些古老的技术文物
然而，它似乎坏了。
但更有趣的是
有一个可疑的装置看起来像电梯还在工作
那个装置把我们带到了一个熟悉的走廊上的房间
但最有趣的是研究站
通过使用它
我们找到了修复古代文物的方法
我们只需要一些好的润滑剂
由（杜坦公地石油？）
在DNA磁盘的帮助下
我们成功提取了制作古代符文电路所需的信息
现在我们可以回到正轨了
建造一些新机器，这将大大提高我们收集和处理材料的能力
为这一切提供动力
我们尝试建造新的涡轮机
但是法老的诅咒导致沙子堵塞了它们
所以我们建造了一个能承受沙子诅咒的超级涡轮机
那个涡轮机也非常需要等离子
所以我们必须建造一个辅助聚变反应堆来跟上它
在建造了足够多的这些之后
我们开始研究在图坦卡蒙尸体上发现的细菌
经过足够的突变
我们设法获得了一个良好的碳氢化合物来源
我们用它来构建Runic流形机械手
这台机器将使用我们新开发的聚变反应堆的产品
折叠我们新的Runic Stargate组装器所需的结构部件
有了它我们就能修复古老的星际之门
这将把我们带到一个更糟糕的地方
我们四处游荡了一段时间
寻找各种液体
但最吸引我们好奇心的是火焰的外壳
研究之后
在一些经过大量加工的下架的帮助下
我们设法建造了一个地狱锻造厂
虽然这不如上帝锻造的好
它仍然产生了一些相当好的血浆
我们用新的量子冷却器冷却下来
但金属加工还是不够快
幸运的是我们收到了来自天空的援助之手
让我们得以建造大型合金熔炉
但是现在我们有太多的东西要冷却
只是量子冷却还不够好
希望将我们的真空冰箱推广到无效冰箱
我们建造了另一个通往最终维度的星门
我们像往常一样开始收集汽油的地方
然后我们进行了一次快速探险，寻找龙头
我们用它来研究我们新的龙输液阵列
有了这个，我们现在可以升级我们的技术
例如48 Block Range无线电力发射器
这不仅使我们能够使用无线能源
还有64安培的舱口
我们还进入了下一层核聚变反应堆
但最重要的是
我们现在可以建造一个比无菌室更干净的房间
这房间的确充满了远古巨龙的气息
允许制造最高水平的严酷技术
最终将是第二层辅助聚变反应堆
能够产生最大的
在快速制作了新机器结构所需的所有零件后
我们终于完成了它并获得了一个新朋友
因为他要跟我们待一段时间
我们去接他好带他参观新家
这是纠正坏男孩的地方
这是我们制作热液体的地方
这是我们制造更热液体的地方
这是我们制作热固体的地方
在它旁边，我们冷却热材料
那是我们的装配线
这是我们的主电池
为我们的电池充电的最高涡轮机
做被动过程的随机机器
随机机器制造我们需要的任何东西
你妈妈
昂贵
旧聚变反应堆的废墟
你的兄弟姐妹
那就是你的新游乐场
请小心，不要扭曲时空的结构